<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!DOCTYPE metadata SYSTEM "http://www.fgdc.gov/metadata/fgdc-std-001-1998.dtd">
<metadata>
	<idinfo>
		<citation>
			<citeinfo>
				<origin>Office of the Chief Technology Officer</origin>
				<pubdate>20111121</pubdate>
				<title>District Agency Location</title>
				<geoform Sync="TRUE">vector digital data</geoform>
				<pubinfo>
					<publish>DC GIS</publish>
				</pubinfo>
				<onlink Sync="TRUE">\\ojsfile1\global\GIS\SPATIAL_DATA\DataCatalog\DCAgencyPt.shp</onlink>
				<lworkcit>
					<citeinfo>
						<origin>DC GIS</origin>
						<title>DC Geographic Information System</title>
						<geoform>vector digital data</geoform>
					</citeinfo>
				</lworkcit>
				<ftname Sync="TRUE">DCAgencyPt</ftname></citeinfo>
		</citation>
		<descript>
			<abstract>DC Government: agency locations. The dataset contains locations and attributes of DC Agencies, created as part of the DC Geographic Information System (DC GIS) for the D.C. Office of the Chief Technology Officer (OCTO) and participating D.C. government agencies.

Databases researched by the DC Office of the Chief Technology Officer (OCTO) identified DC Agency locations and DC GIS staff geo-processed the data.

All DC GIS data is stored and exported in Maryland State Plane coordinates NAD 83 meters.

METADATA CONTENT IS IN PROCESS OF VALIDATION AND SUBJECT TO CHANGE.</abstract>
			<purpose>This data is used for the planning and management of Washington, D.C. by local government agencies.</purpose>
			<langdata Sync="TRUE">en</langdata></descript>
		<timeperd>
			<timeinfo>
				<sngdate>
					<caldate>20111121</caldate>
				</sngdate>
			</timeinfo>
			<current>publication date</current>
		</timeperd>
		<status>
			<progress>Complete</progress>
			<update>As needed</update>
		</status>
		<spdom>
			<bounding>
				<westbc Sync="TRUE">-77.064337</westbc>
				<eastbc Sync="TRUE">-76.947810</eastbc>
				<northbc Sync="TRUE">38.958821</northbc>
				<southbc Sync="TRUE">38.820416</southbc>
			</bounding>
			<dsgpoly>
				<dsgpolyo>
					<grngpoin>
					</grngpoin>
				</dsgpolyo>
			</dsgpoly>
			<lboundng><leftbc Sync="TRUE">394423.740000</leftbc><rightbc Sync="TRUE">404523.470500</rightbc><bottombc Sync="TRUE">128072.860000</bottombc><topbc Sync="TRUE">143434.890000</topbc></lboundng></spdom>
		<keywords>
			<theme>
				<themekt>none</themekt>
				<themekey>Facility</themekey>
				<themekey>Municipal</themekey>
				<themekey>building</themekey>
				<themekey>Facility</themekey>
				<themekey>society</themekey>
				<themekey>DC Government</themekey>
				<themekey>Agency</themekey>
			</theme>
			<place>
				<placekey>Washington, D.C.</placekey>
				<placekey>District of Columbia</placekey>
				<placekey>DC</placekey>
				<placekey>DC GIS</placekey>
				<placekey>DCGIS</placekey>
			</place>
		</keywords>
		<useconst>Acknowledgment of the DC Geographic Information Systems Program (DC GIS).  The District of Columbia Government makes no claims as to the completeness, accuracy or content of any data contained hereon, and makes no representation of any kind, including, but not limited to, the warranty of the accuracy or fitness for a  particular use, nor are any such warranties to be implied or inferred with respect to the information or data furnished herein.</useconst>
		<ptcontac>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>D.C. Office of the Chief Technology Officer</cntorg>
					<cntper>GIS Data Coordinator</cntper>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype>
					<address>441 4th St NW, Suite 930 South</address>
					<city>Washington</city>
					<state>DC</state>
					<postal>20001</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>(202) 727-1761</cntvoice>
				<cntfax>(202) 727-5660</cntfax>
				<cntemail>dcgis@dc.gov</cntemail>
				<hours>8:30 am - 5 pm</hours>
			</cntinfo>
		</ptcontac>
		<datacred>Various sources</datacred>
		<native Sync="TRUE">Microsoft Windows XP Version 5.1 (Build 2600) Service Pack 3; ESRI ArcCatalog 9.3.1.4000</native>
		<natvform Sync="TRUE">Shapefile</natvform></idinfo>
	<dataqual>
		<attracc>
			<attraccr>Data believed to be complete and accurate, subject to change. Digital version compared with original source data for accuracy and completeness. Validated by source and/or responsible agency.</attraccr>
		</attracc>
		<logic>In process of validation by source and/or responsible agency.</logic>
		<complete>Data believed to be complete and accurate, subject to change. Digital version compared with original source data for accuracy and completeness. Validated by source and/or responsible agency.</complete>
		<posacc>
			<horizpa>
				<horizpar>In process of validation by source and/or responsible agency.</horizpar>
			</horizpa>
			<vertacc>
				<vertaccr>N/A</vertaccr>
			</vertacc>
		</posacc>
		<lineage>
			<srcinfo>
				<srccite>
					<citeinfo>
						<origin>DC Government</origin>
						<pubdate>04/18/2003</pubdate>
						<title>DC.gov</title>
						<othercit>OCTO GIS staff culled agencies from web site.</othercit>
						<onlink>http://octo.dc.gov/main.shtm</onlink>
					</citeinfo>
				</srccite>
				<typesrc>web site</typesrc>
				<srctime>
					<timeinfo>
						<sngdate>
							<caldate>04/18/2003</caldate>
						</sngdate>
					</timeinfo>
					<srccurr>publication date</srccurr>
				</srctime>
				<srccitea>DC government homepage</srccitea>
				<srccontr>locations and attributes</srccontr>
			</srcinfo>
			<srcinfo>
				<srccite>
					<citeinfo>
						<origin>Departmet of Employment Services</origin>
						<pubdate>2003</pubdate>
						<title>DOES website</title>
						<onlink>http://does.dc.gov/main.shtm</onlink>
					</citeinfo>
				</srccite>
				<typesrc>online</typesrc>
				<srccitea>DOES website</srccitea>
				<srccontr>location and attributes</srccontr>
			</srcinfo>
			<srcinfo>
				<typesrc>online</typesrc>
				<srccitea>DMV website</srccitea>
				<srccontr>attribute and location</srccontr>
			</srcinfo>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Data Collection:

Through the application's functionality and usability requirements, OCTO GIS staff compose a list of data layers needed for the application.   From this, staff determine the appropriate source and location for each layer, and assess the effort needed to get it.  

Some layers, already part of the DC Atlas, are incorporated into the data store.  For DC agency data, agency liaisons ask DC personnel about data availability and acquisition.  For third-party data, OCTO-GIS evaluates options and either finds alternatives, purchases, or licenses the data.  In some cases, staff create data from existing sources and then add required attribution.</procdesc>
				<procdate>5/31/03</procdate>
				<proccont>
					<cntinfo>
						<cntorgp>
							<cntorg>D.C. Office of the Chief Technology Officer</cntorg>
							<cntper>GIS Data Coordinator</cntper>
						</cntorgp>
						<cntvoice>(202) 727-1761</cntvoice>
						<cntfax>(202) 727-5660</cntfax>
						<cntemail>dcgis@dc.gov</cntemail>
						<hours>8:30 am - 5 pm</hours>
					</cntinfo>
				</proccont>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Data Preparation:

After the collection, the data team prepares the data for qa/qc and inclusion in the data store.  This step involves: 1.) configuring the datasets into a common form; 2.) geocoding tabular data using a common address base;  3.) generating or converting paper documents into digital format; 4.) populating required fields; and 5.) resolving data duplication and conflicts.

For geocoding, staff use a derivative of the Office of Tax and Revenue (OTR) owner-point database and the District Department of Transportation's (DDOT) street inventory system (SIS) street centerline file as the address base.  Through automated procedures on the owner-point derivative file, personnel clean and standardize the irregular premise address information into street number, name, type, and quadrant fields.  Also, staff use the merged SIS file containing the five centerlines classifications (street, alley, drive, service road, and ramp).

First, staff match tabular data to the standardized owner-points.  Then, the rest are matched to the street centerline file.  After this, staff compose a list of the unmatched records needing further research.  Since not all of the records geocode, staff note the final matching figures (number of hits, rejects, and the total).

For web links, team members check the validity of existing links and find matching web sites that directly represent the feature.  Staff use several web search engines to find appropriate web links.  DC government sites are primarily used, when available.

To eliminate data redundancy, staff identify possible conflicting layers and duplicate features.  In some cases, staff pick the best source.  In others, the attributes in the multiple layers are consolidated.  Sometimes, staff map the conflicting layers and investigate feature clusters as areas of potential duplication.

Where applicable, team members move points to the center of the corresponding buildings.  Staff then select the building footprints and assign the appropriate GIS_ID value that links the points with the appropriate building polygon(s).</procdesc>
				<procdate>5/31/03</procdate>
				<proccont>
					<cntinfo>
						<cntorgp>
							<cntorg>D.C. Office of the Chief Technology Officer</cntorg>
							<cntper>GIS Data Coordinator</cntper>
						</cntorgp>
						<cntvoice>(202) 727-1761</cntvoice>
						<cntfax>(202) 727-5660</cntfax>
						<cntemail>dcgis@dc.gov</cntemail>
						<hours>8:30 am - 5 pm</hours>
					</cntinfo>
				</proccont>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Data QA/QC

After data preparation, the data team performs qa/qc.   Various processes check the following parameters: 1.) spatial and attribute accuracy; 2.) data usability; 3.) data dictionary adherence; 4.) specialized metrics, such as connectivity and directionality; and 5.) data load success.  These checks are, as follows:

Visual - staff perform a structured visual check of the data, using on-screen, plotting, and customized routines, and, at times, comparing it to the source documents.

Edge-matching - For grided datasets, staff review the spatial capture, connectivity, and attribution of data across tile boundaries, where applicable.

Automated - Staff compare the data to documented standards and source files through automated procedures and reports.

Specialized - Staff review more specific data parameters, such as directionality, connectivity , and topology.

Edit Verification - Staff ensure that previous errors are fixed to specifications.
?
Field Verification - Occasionally, through field work, team members compare the GIS data with the real world.

Data Loading - Staff evaluate the success and evaluate the process of loading raw data into a structured database.

Since most of the data use addresses as the spatial reference, staff compare the data against base layers (buildings, roads, street centerlines, owner-points, parks, and orthophotography) and move features where needed.

In some cases, OCTO GIS personnel produce maps and reports for source agency review. Through an iterative process, staff modify and enhance the layer to agency specifications.  For some datasets, the agency endorses the final product for data load and publication.</procdesc>
				<procdate>5/31/03</procdate>
				<proccont>
					<cntinfo>
						<cntorgp>
							<cntorg>D.C. Office of the Chief Technology Officer</cntorg>
							<cntper>GIS Data Coordinator</cntper>
						</cntorgp>
						<cntvoice>(202) 727-1761</cntvoice>
						<cntfax>(202) 727-5660</cntfax>
						<cntemail>dcgis@dc.gov</cntemail>
						<hours>8:30 am - 5 pm</hours>
					</cntinfo>
				</proccont>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Final Data Preparation:

For final preparation, staff ensure all of the needed items are present (unneeded items are deleted), the metadata is complete and current, the shapefile is in the proper projection, and a spatial index exists.  If not already done, a GIS_ID (unique id for features in the layer) is computed with automated tools.</procdesc>
				<procdate>5/31/03</procdate>
				<proccont>
					<cntinfo>
						<cntorgp>
							<cntorg>D.C. Office of the Chief Technology Officer</cntorg>
							<cntper>GIS Data Coordinator</cntper>
						</cntorgp>
						<cntvoice>(202) 727-1761</cntvoice>
						<cntfax>(202) 727-5660</cntfax>
						<cntemail>dcgis@dc.gov</cntemail>
						<hours>8:30 am - 5 pm</hours>
					</cntinfo>
				</proccont>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Data Load:

After final preparation, OCTO GIS staff load the data into the application's test database, where SDE handles the spatial data and ORACLE manages the attribute information.

First, staff add primary key and name fields to the layer.  Second, personnel register the layer into the appropriate tables and establish the unique feature-ids (the link between the spatial object and its attributes) specific to that layer.  Then, staff populate feature, search, address, web url, contact, data source, and other tables, where applicable. For point layers, team members calculate each feature's geographic extent and populate the features table.  Lastly, each layer is intersected with the base geography (2002 Advisory Neighborhood Commission areas, 2002 wards, zip codes, neighborhoods, and neighborhood clusters) to populate the "what's-within" tables for the web reports.  Views are refreshed when needed.</procdesc>
				<procdate>5/31/03</procdate>
				<proccont>
					<cntinfo>
						<cntorgp>
							<cntorg>D.C. Office of the Chief Technology Officer</cntorg>
							<cntper>GIS Data Coordinator</cntper>
						</cntorgp>
						<cntvoice>(202) 727-1761</cntvoice>
						<cntfax>(202) 727-5660</cntfax>
						<cntemail>dcgis@dc.gov</cntemail>
						<hours>8:30 am - 5 pm</hours>
					</cntinfo>
				</proccont>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Data Load QA/QC

OCTO GIS performs spatial checks comparing the test SDE database with source files to check for completeness, spatial integrity, and proper attribution.  First, staff compare the test database contents with documented standards.  Then, team members check the geography and attribution, as well as compare dataset parameters between both layers.

The data team performs attribute checks on the ORACLE database to ensure the existence and validity of views.  Again, staff compare the database contents with documented standards.  For critical views, personnel check the view structures and data against source files and documentation.</procdesc>
				<procdate>5/31/03</procdate>
				<proccont>
					<cntinfo>
						<cntorgp>
							<cntorg>D.C. Office of the Chief Technology Officer</cntorg>
							<cntper>GIS Data Coordinator</cntper>
						</cntorgp>
						<cntvoice>(202) 727-1761</cntvoice>
						<cntfax>(202) 727-5660</cntfax>
						<cntemail>dcgis@dc.gov</cntemail>
						<hours>8:30 am - 5 pm</hours>
					</cntinfo>
				</proccont>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Metadata imported.</procdesc>
				<srcused>C:\DOCUME~1\roew\LOCALS~1\Temp\xml1885.tmp</srcused>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Metadata imported.</procdesc>
				<srcused>C:\OCTOGIS\Data\OCTO\DCAgencyPt_old.shp.xml</srcused>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>OCTO GIS staff visited DOES source material to verify and correct the locations of DOES one-stop centers.  Staff deleted the existing locations, replacing them with seven new DOES one-stop sites.</procdesc>
				<procdate>9/15/03</procdate>
				<proccont>
					<cntinfo>
						<cntorgp>
							<cntorg>OCTO</cntorg>
							<cntper>GIS Data Coordinator</cntper>
						</cntorgp>
						<cntvoice>202-727-1761</cntvoice>
						<cntfax>202-727-5660</cntfax>
						<cntemail>dcgis@dc.gov</cntemail>
						<hours>8:30am - 5pm</hours>
					</cntinfo>
				</proccont>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Metadata imported.</procdesc>
				<srcused>E:\DCGISDATA_WORKSPACE\OCTO\DCAgencyPt_old.shp.xml</srcused>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Metadata imported.</procdesc>
				<srcused>C:\temp\DCGIS.xml</srcused>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>DC GIS updated the DC agency point from the directory contained on the dc.gov website and the DMV website.</procdesc>
				<procdate>20081017</procdate>
				<proccont>
					<cntinfo>
						<cntorgp>
							<cntorg>OCTO</cntorg>
						</cntorgp>
					</cntinfo>
				</proccont>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Dataset copied.</procdesc>
				<srcused>Server=10.1.11.144; Service=5151; User=intragis_dcatlas; Version=SDE.DEFAULT</srcused>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>added does sites.</procdesc>
				<procdate>20081229</procdate>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Review the DC.GOV page for district agency location and contact information.  This layer represents primary locations for District Agencies, MVA sites, and other public service locations.  Places such as libraries, fire, and police stations are in other layers.</procdesc>
				<procdate>20100514</procdate>
				<proccont>
					<cntinfo>
						<cntorgp>
							<cntorg>OCTO</cntorg>
						</cntorgp>
					</cntinfo>
				</proccont>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Moved DDOT to 55 M ST SE  and added 414 FARRAGUT ST NW  as a DDOT Maintenance Yard.  Checked the remaining records against the Agency Directory found on the main dc.gov site (locations and web urls).  Employee Appeals office also moved to 1100 4th St SW.</procdesc>
				<procdate>20110513</procdate>
				<proccont>
					<cntinfo>
						<cntorgp>
							<cntorg>OCTO</cntorg>
						</cntorgp>
					</cntinfo>
				</proccont>
			</procstep>
			<procstep>
				<procdesc>Changed the location of two dc agencies:

DOH
899 North Capitol Street, NE
Washington, DC 20002

PERB
1100 4th Street, SW
Suite E630
Washington, DC 20024</procdesc>
				<procdate>20111121</procdate>
				<proccont>
					<cntinfo>
						<cntorgp>
							<cntorg>OCTO</cntorg>
						</cntorgp>
					</cntinfo>
				</proccont>
			</procstep>
			<procstep><procdesc Sync="TRUE">Metadata imported.</procdesc><srcused Sync="TRUE">C:\temp\DCAgencyPt.xml</srcused><procdate Sync="TRUE">20111121</procdate><proctime Sync="TRUE">16063900</proctime></procstep></lineage>
	</dataqual>
	<spdoinfo>
		<direct Sync="TRUE">Vector</direct>
		<ptvctinf>
			<sdtsterm Name="DCAgencyPt">
				<sdtstype Sync="TRUE">Entity point</sdtstype>
				<ptvctcnt Sync="TRUE">148</ptvctcnt>
			</sdtsterm>
			<esriterm Name="DCAgencyPt"><efeatyp Sync="TRUE">Simple</efeatyp><efeageom Sync="TRUE">Point</efeageom><esritopo Sync="TRUE">FALSE</esritopo><efeacnt Sync="TRUE">148</efeacnt><spindex Sync="TRUE">TRUE</spindex><linrefer Sync="TRUE">FALSE</linrefer></esriterm></ptvctinf>
	</spdoinfo>
	<spref>
		<horizsys>
			<planar>
				<planci>
					<plance Sync="TRUE">coordinate pair</plance>
					<coordrep>
						<absres Sync="TRUE">0.000000</absres>
						<ordres Sync="TRUE">0.000000</ordres>
					</coordrep>
					<plandu Sync="TRUE">meters</plandu>
				</planci>
				<gridsys><gridsysn Sync="TRUE">State Plane Coordinate System 1983</gridsysn><spcs><spcszone Sync="TRUE">1900</spcszone><lambertc><stdparll Sync="TRUE">38.300000</stdparll><stdparll Sync="TRUE">39.450000</stdparll><longcm Sync="TRUE">-77.000000</longcm><latprjo Sync="TRUE">37.666667</latprjo><feast Sync="TRUE">400000.000000</feast><fnorth Sync="TRUE">0.000000</fnorth></lambertc></spcs></gridsys></planar>
			<geodetic>
				<horizdn Sync="TRUE">North American Datum of 1983</horizdn>
				<ellips Sync="TRUE">Geodetic Reference System 80</ellips>
				<semiaxis Sync="TRUE">6378137.000000</semiaxis>
				<denflat Sync="TRUE">298.257222</denflat>
			</geodetic>
			<cordsysn><geogcsn Sync="TRUE">GCS_North_American_1983</geogcsn><projcsn Sync="TRUE">NAD_1983_StatePlane_Maryland_FIPS_1900</projcsn></cordsysn></horizsys>
		<vertdef>
			<altsys>
				<altres Sync="TRUE">1.000000</altres>
				<altenc Sync="TRUE">Explicit elevation coordinate included with horizontal coordinates</altenc>
			</altsys>
		</vertdef>
	</spref>
	<eainfo>
		<detailed Name="DCAgencyPt">
			<enttyp>
				<enttypl Sync="TRUE">DCAgencyPt</enttypl>
				<enttypt Sync="TRUE">Feature Class</enttypt><enttypc Sync="TRUE">148</enttypc></enttyp>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>MATCHADDR</attrlabl>
				<attalias Sync="TRUE">FID</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">254</attwidth><attrdef Sync="TRUE">Internal feature number.</attrdef><attrdefs Sync="TRUE">ESRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="TRUE">Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv></attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>X</attrlabl>
				<attalias Sync="TRUE">X</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><attrdef Sync="TRUE">Internal feature number.</attrdef><attrdefs Sync="TRUE">ESRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="TRUE">Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">8</atnumdec></attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>NAME</attrlabl>
				<attalias Sync="TRUE">NAME</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">254</attwidth><attrdef Sync="TRUE">Internal feature number.</attrdef><attrdefs Sync="TRUE">ESRI</attrdefs><attrdomv><udom Sync="TRUE">Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom></attrdomv></attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>Shape</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Feature geometry.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>ESRI</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<udom>Coordinates defining the features.</udom>
				</attrdomv>
				<attalias Sync="TRUE">ID</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">18</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">8</attscale></attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>ID</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Unique ID</attrdef>
				<attalias Sync="TRUE">ADDRESS</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">8</atnumdec></attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>ADDRESS</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Physical location address</attrdef>
				<attalias Sync="TRUE">ABBREV</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">254</attwidth></attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>ABBREV</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Agency abbreviation</attrdef>
				<attalias Sync="TRUE">WEBURL</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">254</attwidth></attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>WEBURL</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Agency website</attrdef>
				<attalias Sync="TRUE">DEPARTMENT</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">254</attwidth></attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>DEPARTMENT</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Agency department</attrdef>
				<attalias Sync="TRUE">OBJECTID</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">254</attwidth></attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>OBJECTID</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Internal feature number.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>ESRI</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<udom>Sequential unique whole numbers that are automatically generated.</udom>
				</attrdomv>
				<attalias Sync="TRUE">Shape</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">8</atnumdec></attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>SHAPE</attrlabl>
				<attrdef>Feature geometry.</attrdef>
				<attrdefs>ESRI</attrdefs>
				<attrdomv>
					<udom>Coordinates defining the features.</udom>
				</attrdomv>
				<attalias Sync="TRUE">ADDRID</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Double</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">10</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">10</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>ADDRID</attrlabl>
				<attalias Sync="TRUE">Y</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">10</attwidth></attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>AddrID</attrlabl>
				<attalias Sync="TRUE">MATCHADDR</attalias><attrtype Sync="TRUE">String</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">254</attwidth><atprecis Sync="TRUE">0</atprecis><attscale Sync="TRUE">0</attscale></attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>Y</attrlabl>
				<attrtype Sync="TRUE">Number</attrtype><attwidth Sync="TRUE">19</attwidth><atnumdec Sync="TRUE">8</atnumdec></attr>
			<attr>
				<attrlabl>MatchAddr</attrlabl>
			</attr>
		</detailed>
	</eainfo>
	<distinfo>
		<distrib>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>D.C. Office of the Chief Technology Officer</cntorg>
					<cntper>GIS Data Coordinator</cntper>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype>
					<address>441 4th St NW, Suite 930 South</address>
					<city>Washington</city>
					<state>DC</state>
					<postal>20001</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>(202) 727-1761</cntvoice>
				<cntfax>(202) 727-5660</cntfax>
				<cntemail>dcgis@dc.gov</cntemail>
				<hours>8:30 am - 5 pm</hours>
			</cntinfo>
		</distrib>
		<resdesc>Downloadable Data</resdesc>
		<distliab>Acknowledgment of the DC Geographic Information Systems Program (DC GIS).  The District of Columbia Government makes no claims as to the completeness, accuracy or content of any data contained hereon, and makes no representation of any kind, including, but not limited to, the warranty of the accuracy or fitness for a  particular use, nor are any such warranties to be implied or inferred with respect to the information or data furnished herein.</distliab>
		<stdorder>
			<digform>
				<digtinfo>
					<transize>0.008</transize>
					<dssize Sync="TRUE">0.004</dssize></digtinfo>
				<digtopt>
					<onlinopt>
						<computer>
							<networka>
							</networka>
						</computer>
					</onlinopt>
				</digtopt>
			</digform>
			<ordering>Contact OCTO GIS.</ordering>
		</stdorder>
	</distinfo>
	<metainfo>
		<metd Sync="TRUE">20120131</metd>
		<metc>
			<cntinfo>
				<cntorgp>
					<cntorg>D.C. Office of the Chief Technology Officer</cntorg>
					<cntper>GIS Data Coordinator</cntper>
				</cntorgp>
				<cntaddr>
					<addrtype>mailing and physical address</addrtype>
					<address>441 4th St NW, Suite 930 South</address>
					<city>Washington</city>
					<state>DC</state>
					<postal>20001</postal>
					<country>USA</country>
				</cntaddr>
				<cntvoice>(202) 727-1761</cntvoice>
				<cntfax>(202) 727-5660</cntfax>
				<cntemail>dcgis@dc.gov</cntemail>
				<hours>8:30 am - 5 pm</hours>
			</cntinfo>
		</metc>
		<metstdn Sync="TRUE">FGDC Content Standards for Digital Geospatial Metadata</metstdn>
		<metstdv Sync="TRUE">FGDC-STD-001-1998</metstdv>
		<mettc Sync="TRUE">local time</mettc>
		<metextns>
			<onlink>http://www.esri.com/metadata/esriprof80.html</onlink>
			<metprof>ESRI Metadata Profile</metprof>
		</metextns>
		<metextns>
			<onlink>http://www.esri.com/metadata/esriprof80.html</onlink>
			<metprof>ESRI Metadata Profile</metprof>
		</metextns>
		<langmeta Sync="TRUE">en</langmeta><metextns><onlink Sync="TRUE">http://www.esri.com/metadata/esriprof80.html</onlink><metprof Sync="TRUE">ESRI Metadata Profile</metprof></metextns></metainfo>
	<Esri><MetaID>{50D737B0-4449-4468-B25F-AC81DE955765}</MetaID><CreaDate>20111121</CreaDate><CreaTime>16063900</CreaTime><SyncOnce>FALSE</SyncOnce><SyncDate>20120131</SyncDate><SyncTime>13564700</SyncTime><ModDate>20120131</ModDate><ModTime>13564700</ModTime><DataProperties><lineage><Process ToolSource="C:\Program Files\ArcGIS\ArcToolbox\Toolboxes\Data Management Tools.tbx\CopyFeatures" Date="20120131" Time="105705">CopyFeatures DCGIS.DCAgencyPt G:\GIS\SPATIAL_DATA\DataCatalog\DCGIS_DCAgencyPt.shp # 0 0 0</Process></lineage></DataProperties></Esri><dataIdInfo><envirDesc Sync="TRUE">Microsoft Windows XP Version 5.1 (Build 2600) Service Pack 3; ESRI ArcCatalog 9.3.1.4000</envirDesc><dataLang><languageCode Sync="TRUE" value="en"></languageCode></dataLang><idCitation><resTitle Sync="TRUE">DCAgencyPt</resTitle><presForm><PresFormCd Sync="TRUE" value="005"></PresFormCd></presForm></idCitation><spatRpType><SpatRepTypCd Sync="TRUE" value="001"></SpatRepTypCd></spatRpType><dataExt><geoEle><GeoBndBox esriExtentType="native"><westBL Sync="TRUE">394423.74</westBL><eastBL Sync="TRUE">404523.4705</eastBL><northBL Sync="TRUE">143434.89</northBL><southBL Sync="TRUE">128072.86</southBL><exTypeCode Sync="TRUE">1</exTypeCode></GeoBndBox></geoEle></dataExt><geoBox esriExtentType="decdegrees"><westBL Sync="TRUE">-77.064337</westBL><eastBL Sync="TRUE">-76.94781</eastBL><northBL Sync="TRUE">38.958821</northBL><southBL Sync="TRUE">38.820416</southBL><exTypeCode Sync="TRUE">1</exTypeCode></geoBox></dataIdInfo><mdLang><languageCode Sync="TRUE" value="en"></languageCode></mdLang><mdStanName Sync="TRUE">ISO 19115 Geographic Information - Metadata</mdStanName><mdStanVer Sync="TRUE">DIS_ESRI1.0</mdStanVer><mdChar><CharSetCd Sync="TRUE" value="004"></CharSetCd></mdChar><mdHrLv><ScopeCd Sync="TRUE" value="005"></ScopeCd></mdHrLv><mdHrLvName Sync="TRUE">dataset</mdHrLvName><distInfo><distributor><distorTran><onLineSrc><orDesc Sync="TRUE">002</orDesc><linkage Sync="TRUE">file://\\ojsfile1\global\GIS\SPATIAL_DATA\DataCatalog\DCAgencyPt.shp</linkage><protocol Sync="TRUE">Local Area Network</protocol></onLineSrc><transSize Sync="TRUE">0.004</transSize></distorTran><distorFormat><formatName Sync="TRUE">Shapefile</formatName></distorFormat></distributor></distInfo><refSysInfo><RefSystem><refSysID><identCode Sync="TRUE">NAD_1983_StatePlane_Maryland_FIPS_1900</identCode></refSysID></RefSystem></refSysInfo><spatRepInfo><VectSpatRep><topLvl><TopoLevCd Sync="TRUE" value="001"></TopoLevCd></topLvl><geometObjs Name="DCAgencyPt"><geoObjTyp><GeoObjTypCd Sync="TRUE" value="004"></GeoObjTypCd></geoObjTyp><geoObjCnt Sync="TRUE">148</geoObjCnt></geometObjs></VectSpatRep></spatRepInfo><mdDateSt Sync="TRUE">20120131</mdDateSt></metadata>
